Guide to the HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm, 1907-1993
HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1981-1982.
  - Local 873., 1982; 228 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02730 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 878., 1981; 229 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02736 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 878., 1982; 230 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02805 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 879., 1981; 231 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02862 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 879., 1982; 232 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02894 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 879. Loan., 1982; 233 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 02948 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 886., 1981; 234 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 03050 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 886., 1982; 235 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 03065 on Correspondence reel 2.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1983-1987.
  - Local 1., 1983-1987; 1 (Reel 42)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 3.
  - Local 2, 1983-1987; 2 (Reel 42)
    Beginning at frame 00247 on Correspondence reel 3.
  - Local 3., 1983-1987; 3 (Reel 42)
    Beginning at frame 00614 on Correspondence reel 3.
  - Local 4, 1983-1987; 4 (Reel 42)
    Beginning at frame 00709 on Correspondence reel 3.
  - Local 5, 1983-1987; 5 (Reel 42)
    Beginning at frame 00770 on Correspondence reel 3.
  - Local 6, 1983-1987; 6 (Reel 42)
    Beginning at frame 00841 on Correspondence reel 3.
  - Local 7, 1983-1987; 7 (Reel 42)
    Beginning at frame 01037 on Correspondence reel 3.
  - Local 8, 1983-1987; 8 (Reel 42)
    Beginning at frame 01131 on Correspondence reel 3.
  - Local 9, 1983-1987; 9 (Reel 42)
    Beginning at frame 01520 on Correspondence reel 3.
  - Local 10, 1983-1987; 10 (Reel 42)
    Beginning at frame 01708 on Correspondence reel 3.
  - Local 11, 1983-1987; 11 (Reel 42)
    Beginning at frame 01781 on Correspondence reel 3.
  - Local 12, 1983-1987; 1 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 14, 1983-1987; 2 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00161 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 15, 1983-1987; 3 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00199 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 16, 1983-1987; 4 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00411 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 17, 1983-1987; 5 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00500 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 18, 1983-1987; 6 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00618 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 19, 1983-1987; 7 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00680 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 20, 1983-1987; 8 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00840 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 21, 1983-1987; 9 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00856 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 23, 1983-1987; 10 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00904 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 24, 1983-1987; 11 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00929 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 25, 1983-1987; 12 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 01114 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 26, 1983-1987; 13 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 01291 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 27, 1983-1987; 14 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 01426 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 28, 1983-1987; 15 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 01454 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 29, 1983-1987; 16 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 01608 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 30, 1983-1987; 17 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 00169 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 31, 1983-1987; 18 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 01709 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 34, 1983-1987; 19 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 01787 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 35, 1983-1987; 20 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 02046 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 40, 1983-1987; 21 (Reel 43)
    Beginning at frame 02169 on Correspondence reel 4.
  - Local 43, 1983-1987; 1 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 46, 1983-1987; 2 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00070 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 47, 1983-1987; 3 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00079 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 49, 1983-1987; 4 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00178 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 50, 1983-1987; 5 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00292 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 51, 1983-1987; 6 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00383 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 54, 1983-1987; 7 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00403 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 56, 1983-1987; 8 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00574 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 57, 1983-1987; 9 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00617 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 62, 1983-1987; 10 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00668 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 64, 1983-1987; 11 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00734 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 65, 1983-1987; 12 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00824 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 69, 1983-1987; 13 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 00879 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 70, 1983-1987; 14 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 01073 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 74, 1983-1987; 15 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 01162 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 75, 1983-1987; 16 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 01218 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 76, 1983-1987; 17 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 01413 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 83, 1983-1987; 18 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 01433 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 84, 1983-1987; 19 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 01449 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 86, 1983-1987; 20 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 01509 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 88, 1983-1987; 21 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 01641 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 99, 1983-1987; 22 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 01760 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 100, 1983-1987; 23 (Reel 44)
    Beginning at frame 01796 on Correspondence reel 5.
  - Local 101, 1983-1987; 1 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 104, 1983-1987; 2 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00046 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 118, 1983-1987; 3 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00054 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 122, 1983-1987; 4 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00088 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 123, 1983-1987; 5 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00199 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 126, 1983-1987; 6 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00203 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 134, 1983-1987; 7 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00221 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 135, 1983-1987; 8 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00265 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 136, 1983-1987; 9 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00337 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 146, 1983-1987; 10 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00367 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 150, 1983-1987; 11 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00407 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 151, 1983-1987; 12 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00499 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 155, 1983-1987; 13 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00537 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 165, 1983-1987; 14 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00545 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 166, 1983-1987; 15 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00623 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 181, 1983-1987; 16 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00664 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 200, 1983-1987; 17 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00685 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 206, 1983-1987; 18 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00703 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 217, 1983-1987; 19 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00748 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 220, 1983-1987; 20 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00864 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 225, 1983-1987; 21 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00915 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 226., 1983-1987; 22 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 00938 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 246, 1983-1987; 23 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01181 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 251, 1983-1987; 24 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01234 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 261, 1983-1987; 25 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01290 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 264, 1983-1987; 26 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01337 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 267, 1983-1987; 27 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01385 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 270, 1983-1987; 28 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01396 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 272, 1983-1987; 29 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01449 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 274, 1983-1987; 30 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01467 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 279, 1983-1987; 31 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01521 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 280, 1983-1987; 32 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01528 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 281, 1983-1987; 33 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01564 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 298, 1983-1987; 34 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01567 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 301, 1983-1987; 35 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01645 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 309, 1983-1987; 36 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01713 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 310, 1983-1987; 37 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01857 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 312, 1983-1987; 38 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01874 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 315, 1983-1987; 39 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01917 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 322, 1983-1987; 40 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01948 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 336, 1983-1987; 41 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 01969 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 340, 1983-1987; 42 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 02000 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 353, 1983-1987; 43 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 02032 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 355, 1983-1987; 44 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 02091 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 360, 1983-1987; 45 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 02174 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 361, 1983-1987; 46 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 02209 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 369, 1983-1987; 47 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 02212 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 391, 1983-1987; 48 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 02225 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 397, 1983-1987; 49 (Reel 45)
    Beginning at frame 02246 on Correspondence reel 6.
  - Local 400, 1983-1987; 1 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 414, 1983-1987; 2 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00047 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 417, 1983-1987; 3 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00067 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 427, 1983-1987; 4 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00095 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 436, 1983-1987; 5 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00154 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 441, 1983-1987; 6 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00210 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 442, 1983-1987; 7 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00232 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 450, 1983-1987; 8 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00280 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 453, 1983-1987; 9 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00338 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 457, 1983-1987; 10 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00348 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 465, 1983-1987; 11 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00397 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 466, 1983-1987; 12 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00409 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 471, 1983-1987; 13 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00433 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 479, 1983-1987; 14 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00512 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 483, 1983-1987; 15 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00517 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 495, 1983-1987; 16 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00568 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 497, 1983-1987; 17 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00576 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 498, 1983-1987; 18 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00589 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 509, 1983-1987; 19 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00630 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 517, 1983-1987; 20 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00636 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 531, 1983-1987; 21 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00688 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 533, 1983-1987; 22 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00789 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 535, 1983-1987; 23 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 00833 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 541, 1983-1987; 24 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01032 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 550, 1983-1987; 25 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01036 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 570, 1983-1987; 26 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01065 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 590, 1983-1987; 27 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01068 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 604, 1983-1987; 28 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01106 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 610, 1983-1987; 29 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01125 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 623, 1983-1987; 30 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01182 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 628, 1983-1987; 31 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01199 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 631, 1983-1987; 32 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01243 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 634, 1983-1987; 33 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01285 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 636, 1983-1987; 34 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01298 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 657, 1983-1987; 35 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01326 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 662, 1983-1987; 36 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01349 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 681, 1983-1987; 37 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01382 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 688, 1983-1987; 38 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01484 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 703, 1983-1987; 39 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01504 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 719, 1983-1987; 40 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01560 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 727, 1983-1987; 41 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01575 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 737, 1983-1987; 42 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01605 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 741, 1983-1987; 43 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01631 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 746, 1983-1987; 44 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01655 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 767, 1983-1987; 45 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01684 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 772, 1983-1987; 46 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01812 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 775, 1983-1987; 47 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01843 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 779, 1983-1987; 48 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01882 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 791, 1983-1987; 49 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01917 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 803, 1983-1987; 50 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01960 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 804, 1983-1987; 51 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 01986 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 806, 1983-1987; 52 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 02010 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 810, 1983-1987; 53 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 02070 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 814, 1983-1987; 54 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 02096 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 838, 1983-1987; 55 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 02179 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 847, 1983-1987; 56 (Reel 46)
    Beginning at frame 02195 on Correspondence reel 7.
  - Local 863, 1983-1987; 1 (Reel 47)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 8.
  - Local 878, 1983-1987; 2 (Reel 47)
    Beginning at frame 00039 on Correspondence reel 8.
  - Local 879, 1983-1987; 3 (Reel 47)
    Beginning at frame 00222 on Correspondence reel 8.
  - Local 886, 1983-1987; 4 (Reel 47)
    Beginning at frame 00302 on Correspondence reel 8.
  - P.S.S.D.C., 1983-1987; 5 (Reel 47)
    Beginning at frame 00320 on Correspondence reel 8.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1988-1990.
  - Local 1., 1988-1990; 1 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 2, 1988-1990; 2 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00056 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 2. Stake File., 1988-1990; 3 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00110 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 3., 1988-1990; 4 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00276 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 4, 1988-1990; 5 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00310 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 5, 1988-1990; 6 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00343 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 6, 1988-1990; 7 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00412 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 7, 1988-1990; 8 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00469 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 8, 1988-1990; 9 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00530 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 9, 1988-1990; 10 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00678 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 10, 1988-1990; 11 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00720 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 11, 1988; 12 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00734 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 11, 1989-1990; 13 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 00972 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 12, 1988-1990; 14 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01234 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 14, 1988-1990; 15 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01271 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 15, 1988-1990; 16 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01299 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 16, 1988-1990; 17 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01351 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 17, 1988-1990; 18 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01404 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 18, 1988-1990; 19 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01472 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 19, 1988-1990; 20 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01476 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 20, 1988-1990; 21 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01518 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 21, 1988-1990; 22 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01548 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 24, 1988-1990; 23 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01576 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 25, 1988-1990; 24 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01666 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 26, 1988-1990; 25 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01818 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 28, 1988-1990; 26 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 01937 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 29, 1988-1990; 27 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 02153 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 30, 1988-1990; 28 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 02158 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 31, 1988-1990; 29 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 02268 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 32, 1988-1990; 30 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 02295 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 34, 1988-1990; 31 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 02389 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 35, 1988-1990; 32 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 02426 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 36, 1988-1990; 33 (Reel 48)
    Beginning at frame 02437 on Correspondence reel 9.
  - Local 43, 1988-1990; 1 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 46, 1988-1990; 2 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00037 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 47, 1988-1990; 3 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00040 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 49, 1988-1990; 4 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00060 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 50, 1988-1990; 5 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00121 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 51, 1988-1990; 6 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00152 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 54, 1988-1990; 7 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00178 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 56, 1988-1990; 8 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00248 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 56. Strike File., 1988-1990; 9 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00279 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 57, 1988-1990; 10 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00355 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 62, 1988-1990; 11 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00386 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 64, 1988-1990; 12 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00431 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 65, 1988-1990; 13 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00622 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 69, 1988-1990; 14 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00663 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 70, 1988-1990; 15 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00757 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 72, 1988-1990; 16 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00797 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 73, 1988-1990; 17 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00800 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 74, 1988-1990; 18 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00807 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 75, 1988-1990; 19 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00842 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 76, 1988-1990; 20 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00959 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 84, 1988-1990; 21 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 00965 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 86, 1988-1990; 22 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01015 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 88, 1988-1990; 23 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01055 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 99, 1988-1990; 24 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01102 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 100, 1988-1990; 25 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01131 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 101, 1988-1990; 26 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01363 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 104, 1988-1990; 27 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01379 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 105, 1988-1990; 28 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01393 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 118, 1988-1990; 29 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01398 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 122, 1988-1990; 30 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01416 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 126, 1988-1990; 31 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01457 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 135, 1988-1990; 32 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01478 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 146, 1988-1990; 33 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01552 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 150, 1988-1990; 34 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01562 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 151, 1988-1990; 35 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01666 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 155, 1988-1990; 36 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01679 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 165, 1988-1990; 37 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01687 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 166, 1988-1990; 38 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01764 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 200, 1988-1990; 39 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01771 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 206, 1988-1990; 40 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01787 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 215, 1988-1990; 41 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01824 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 217, 1988-1990; 42 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01831 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 220, 1988-1990; 43 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01864 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 225, 1988-1990; 44 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01875 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 226., 1988; 45 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 01877 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 226., 1989-1990; 46 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 02055 on Correspondence reel 10.
  - Local 246, 1988-1990; 47 (Reel 49)
    Beginning at frame 02196 on Correspondence reel 10.